londoneye.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy

This web site is owned and run by London Eye Management Services Limited ("Coca-Cola London Eye"), a division of Merlin Entertainments Group. Coca-Cola London Eye recognises that your privacy is important, and is committed to preserving it. This policy sets out our policy in relation to any personal information which you supply to us through your use of this website. 

Coca-Cola London Eye makes every effort to maintain customer confidentiality when securing an online payment. This includes ensuring the security of your credit card details and other personal information. All of your personal information is encrypted as it travels over the Internet. 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Merlin Entertainments Group Limited ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with any other terms of use available on our website and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Merlin Entertainments Group Limited of 3 Market Close, Poole, Dorset BH15 1NQ.

 **INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

• Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.londoneye.com. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services.   
• We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.  
• If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.  
• We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.  
• Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your bookings including your credit/debit card details.  
• Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.   
• Your name, address, telephone number and/or email address in order to contact you with details of your booking or in the unlikely event that we need to contact you urgently about your booking.

 **IP ADDRESSES**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. Your IP address may also be used to diagnose problems with our server, monitor visitor traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and improve our site further.

 **COOKIES**

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie policy. 

**WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.  
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

 **USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

• To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.   
• To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.   
• To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.  
• To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.  
• To notify you about changes to our service.  
• We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post or telephone.  
• If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.   
• If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.   
• Your data will not be used in this way and we will not pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes unless you tick the relevant box located on http://www.londoneye.com/NewsAndEvents/eNewsletter/Signup.aspx.

 **DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

• In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.  
• If Merlin Entertainments Group Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.  
• If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation.

 **YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at comments@merlinentertainmenrts.biz   
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

 **ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

 **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

 **CONTACT**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to comments@merlinentertainments.biz
